Harold Stein Filk Collection
Harold Stein Filk Archive
- Conventions
  - Boskone
    - Boskone 49, 2012
      - Helmuth: Speaking for Boskone 49 #2, 2012; 1 copy; Notes: Blue paper, double sided Convention: Boskone 49: 2012; genreform: Newsletter (Box 14)
        Convention -- Boskone 49 (2012); Newsletter
      - Helmuth: Speaking for Boskone 49, #1, 2012; 1 copy; Notes: Yellow paper, double sided Convention: Boskone 49: 2012; genreform: Newsletter (Box 14)
      - Moderator guide, 2012; 1 copy; Notes: White single sided page Convention: Boskone 49: 2012; genreform: Convention Documents (Box 14)
      - Welcome to Boskone 49 - Program participant welcome, 2012; 1 copy; Notes: White single sided page Convention: Boskone 49: 2012; genreform: Convention Documents (Box 14)
    - Boskone 51, 14 Feb 2014 to 16 Feb 2014
      - Helmuth newsletter, Volume 51, issue 1, 2014; Boskone (51: 2014); 1 copy; Notes: Friday edition Convention: Boskone 51: 2014; genreform: Newsletter (Box 9)
        Convention -- Boskone 51 (2014); Newsletter
      - Helmuth newsletter, Volume 51, issue 2, 2014; Boskone (51: 2014); 1 copy; Notes: Satuday edition Convention: Boskone 51: 2014; genreform: Newsletter (Box 9)
      - Helmuth newsletter, Volume 51, issue 3, 2014; Boskone (51: 2014); 1 copy; Notes: Saturday night edition Convention: Boskone 51: 2014; genreform: Newsletter (Box 9)
      - Helmuth newsletter, Volume 51, issue 4, 2014; Boskone (51: 2014); 1 copy; Notes: Sunday edition Convention: Boskone 51: 2014; genreform: Newsletter (Box 9)
      - Boskone 51, 2014; 1 copy; Notes: Origin: February 14-16, 2014 Convention: Boskone 51; genreform: Pocket Program (Box 9)
        Convention -- Boskone 51 (2014); Program book -- Pocket program
    - Boskone 52, 13 Feb 2015 to 15 Feb 2015
      - Boskone 52 Program Book, 2015; Boskone (52: 2015); 1 copy; Origin: February 13-15, 2015 Convention: Boskone 52; genreform: Program Book (Box 9)
        Convention -- Boskone 52; Program Book
      - Helmuth newsletter, Volume 52, issue 4, 2015; Boskone (52: 2015); 1 copy; Notes: Sunday edition Origin: February 13-15, 2015 Convention: Boskone 52; genreform: Newsletter (Box 9)
        Convention -- Boskone 52; Newsletter
      - Boskone 52, 2015; Boskone (52: 2015); 1 copy; Origin: Boskone 52, February 13-15, 2015 Convention: Boskone 52; genreform: Program Book (Box 9)
    - Boskone
      - Boskone Saturday Night, Boskone; 2 copy; Notes: Featuring filkers, Sassafrass, Bill Roper, Lady Mondegreen Convention: Boskone, February 15; genreform: Program (Box 9)
        Convention -- Boskone, February 15; Program
  - British Filk Convention
    - 14, Contabile Fortean, 01 Feb 2002 to 03 Feb 2002
    - 20, 2t0nic, 01 Feb 2008 to 03 Feb 2008
      - 2t0nic MP3 Backup, 2t0nic; 1 copy; Notes: Origin: UK Filk Con soundboard feed Convention: 2t0nic; genreform: Burnt CD (Box 4)
        Convention -- British Filk Convention. 20, 2t0nic (2008); CD -- Burnt
    - 23, Cre2c3ndo, 04 Feb 2011 to 06 Feb 2011
    - 21, aXXIdental, 2009
      - On the Filk Road: an aXXIdental songbook, 2009; 1 copy; Notes: Black and white cover with fantasy tropes, ISBN 978-1-870824-55-2, edited by Alison Richards Origin: Beccon Publications, January 2009 in-print (same version/edition): http://www.beccon.org/B/filkroad.html Convention: British Filk Convention 21, aXXIdental: 2009; genreform: Songbook (Box 14)
        Convention -- British Filk Convention. 21, aXXIdental (2009); Songbook
    - 19, D'Zenove, 2nd - 4th February 2007
      - Publicity flier for D'zenove Convention, 2011; British Filk Convention, 2011; 1 copy; Notes: One sided, four color Origin: D'zenove Convention, February 2007 Convention: British Filk Convention, 2011; genreform: Flier (Box 10)
        Convention -- British Filk Convention. 23, Cre2c3ndo (2011); Flier; Convention -- D'Zenove
      - 2007 UK Filkcon Raw Recordings from Net 2/07, D'Zenove; 1 copy; Notes: Origin: UK Filk Con soundboard feed Convention: D'Zenove; genreform: Burnt CD (Box 4)
        Convention -- D'Zenove; CD -- Burnt
  - ConChord
    - ConChord 1, 11 Mar 1983 to 13 Mar 1983
      - Con-Chord 5.1, 1983; 1 copy; Notes: Space suited person singing with hedgehogs and robot playing piano. Light blue cover. Staple bound Origin: Convention: Con-Chord 5.1; genreform: Songbook|Program Book (Box 16)
        Convention -- Con-Chord 5.1; Songbook; Program Book
    - ConChord 2, 01 Mar 1985 to 03 Mar 1985
      - ConChord2 - Mister Author, E Mason - Windycon 2006 - Hiss removed, Joey Shoji @FKO 2002, ConChord 2, Windycon 2006, FKO 2002; 1 copy; Notes: .waves of concerts and a tape rip Origin: Possibly Mark Peters Convention: ConChord 2, Windycon 2006, FKO 2002; genreform: Burnt CD (Box 4)
        Convention -- ConChord 2 (1985); Convention -- FilkONtario 12 (2002); Convention -- Windycon 2006, FKO 2002; CD -- Burnt
    - ConChord 8, 02 Oct 1992 to 04 Oct 1992
      - What the Heck is Filk Music/The Filking Time fanzine ad and subscription form, Smith, Nick; 1 copy; Notes: Blue, double sied Origin: Convention: ConChord 8; genreform: Leaflet (Box 2)
        Convention -- ConChord 8 (1992); Leaflet
      - Kazoo Awards Ballot Totally Tasteless and Tacky Review, 1992; ConChord 1992; 1 copy; Notes: White, single sided Origin: ConChord 1992 Convention: ConChord 1992; genreform: Ballot (Box 2)
        Convention -- ConChord 8 (1992); Ballot
    - Con-Chord Concert, ConChord One (March 11-13, 1983); 1 copy; Notes: Origin: Recorded Live at Con-Chord One (Filkcon 5.1) Convention: Con-Chord One; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 2)
      Convention -- Con-Chord One; CD -- Commercial
    - ConChord, 2005; 1 copy; Notes: Pink cover with dancer, cat and computer mouse, staple bound Origin: in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/conchordbook.html Convention: ConChord 19: 2005; genreform: Songbook (Box 14)
      Convention -- ConChord 19 (2005); Songbook
    - Possibly a schedule from ConChord, unknown year., ConChord, unknown year; 1 copy; Notes: White, single sided Origin: Convention: ConChord, unknown year; genreform: Schedule Grid (Box 2)
      Convention -- ConChord; Schedule Grid
    - Con-Chord 5.1, 1983; 1 copy; Notes: Space suited person singing with hedgehogs and robot playing piano. Light blue cover. Staple bound Origin: Convention: Con-Chord 5.1; genreform: Songbook|Program Book (Box 14)
  - Conflikt
    - Conflikt 1, 25 Jan 2008 to 27 Jan 2008
      Washington (state)
      - The Conflikt 1 Special CD, Friday, January 25, 2008; 2008; Conflikt 1 (2008); Recorded and Engineered by John Se; 1 copy; Notes: Origin: Recorded on Friday, January 25, 2008. Recorded and Engineered by John Se Convention: Conflikt 1; genreform: Premium CD (Box 6)
        Convention -- Conflikt 1 (2008); CD -- Premium
      - Conflikt 1 Program book, 2007; 1 copy; Notes: Frogs filking on the Space Needle, staple bound, booklet Origin: Convention: Conflikt 1; genreform: Program booklet (Box 14)
        Convention -- Conflikt 1 (2008); Program booklet
      - The Conflikt 1 Songbook, 2008; 1 copy; Notes: White cover with Mount Renier, staple bound Origin: Convention: Conflikt 1: 2008; genreform: Songbook (Box 14)
        Convention -- Conflikt 1 (2008); Songbook
    - Conflikt 3, 29 Jan 2010 to 31 Jan 2010
      - Conflikt 3 Brunch CD, 2010; Conflikt 3 (2010); 1,8,9 Recorded at Wayward Coffeehouse 12 recorded in Vancouver, BC All others recorded at Conflikt 3.; 1 copy; Notes: Origin: 1,8,9 Recorded at Wayward Coffeehouse 12 recorded in Vancouver, BC All others recorded at Conflikt 3. Convention: Conflikt 3; genreform: Premium CD (Box 6)
        Convention -- Conflikt 3 (2010); CD -- Premium
      - Conflikt III Songbook, 2010; 5 copy; Notes: White cover with dragon contstellation, staple bound, artwork is ""Starstruck"" by Jasmine Turner Origin: Convention: Conflikt 3: 2010; genreform: Songbook (Box 16)
        Convention -- Conflikt 3 (2010); Songbook
    - Conflikt 4, 28 Jan 2011 to 30 Jan 2011
      - Conflikt 4 Brunch CD, 2011; Seghers, John; Kilmer, Jen; 1 copy; Notes: Recorded and engineered by John Seghers and Jen Kilmer except My Low Stat and Magnus Retail. Origin: Recorded at Conflikt 1, 2, 3 and 4, Orycon 2011, Wayward Coffeehouse and The Vault Convention: Conflikt 4; genreform: Premium CD (Box 6)
        CD -- Premium; Convention -- Conflikt 1 (2008); Convention -- Conflikt 2 (2009); Convention -- Conflikt 3 (2010); Convention -- Conflikt 4 (2011); Convention -- Orycon (2011)
      - Conflikt 4, 2011, Conflikt 4 (2011); 1 copy; Notes: Woman on the front with piano keys in a circle. Origin: Conflikt 4, 2011 Convention: Conflikt 4, 2011; genreform: Program booklet (Box 7)
        Convention -- Conflikt 4 (2011); Program booklet
      - The Conflikt IV Songbook, 2011; 1 copy; Notes: White cover with occult symbols, staple bound Origin: Convention: Conflikt 4: 2011; genreform: Songbook (Box 14)
        Convention -- Conflikt 4 (2011); Songbook
      - Walk In The Day, Ben Newman and friends; 4 copy; Notes: Origin: Recording of a play at a filk convention Convention: Conflikt 4; genreform: Private recording (Box 1)
        Convention -- Conflikt 4 (2011); Private recording
      - Cast list for Walk in the Day, Ben Newman and friends; Harold Stein; 1 copy; Notes: Origin: Harold wrote it. Convention: Conflikt 4; genreform: Handwitten paper (Box 1)
        Convention -- Conflikt 4 (2011); Handwitten paper
    - Conflikt 5, 2012
      - Conflikt 5 Songbook, Jan 27-29, 2012; 2 copy; Notes: Parchment cover with person and baby looking out window at the earth, staple bound Origin: Convention: Conflikt 5; genreform: Songbook (Box 14)
        Convention -- Conflikt 5 (2012); Songbook
      - Conflikt Program Book, 2012; 4 copy; Notes: Color cover with rainbow filkers. Staple bound Origin: Convention: Conflikt 5: 2012; genreform: Program Book (Box 14)
        Convention -- Conflikt 5 (2012); Program Book
    - Conflikt 6, 2013
      - Conflikt 6 Program book, 1 copy; Notes: White cover with frogs and pictures of the guests, pamphlet form, staple bound Origin: Convention: Conflikt 6: 2013; genreform: Program Book (Box 16)
        Convention -- Conflikt 6 (2013); Program Book
      - Conflikt 6 Songbook, 2013; 2 copy; Notes: White cover with contorting animal forming a treble clef Origin: Convention: Conflikt 6: 2013; genreform: Songbook (Box 16)
        Convention -- Conflikt 6 (2013); Songbook
    - Conflikt 7, 24 Jan 2014 to 26 Jan 2014
      - Conflikt 7 Songbook, 2014; 3 copy; Notes: Frog sitting on frog cover, staple bound Origin: Convention: Conflikt 7; genreform: Songbook (Box 14)
        Convention -- Conflikt 7 (2014); Songbook
      - Conflikt 7, 2014; Conflikt 7 (2014); 3 copy; Notes: White cover with standard frog logo Origin: Conflikt 7, January 24-26, 2014 Convention: Conflikt 7, January 24-26, 2014; genreform: Songbook (Box 9)
    - Conflikt 8, 30 Jan 2015 to 01 Feb 2015
      - Conflikt 2015, Conflikt 8 (2015); 1 copy; Notes: Origin: Conflikt 2015 Convention: Conflikt 2015, January 30 - February 1; genreform: Program booklet (Box 7)
        Convention -- Conflikt 8 (2015); Program booklet
      - Conflikt 8 Pocket Program, 2015; Conflikt 8 (2015); 1 copy; Notes: Origin: Conflikt 8, January 30 - February 1, 2015 Convention: Conflikt 8; genreform: Pocket Program (Box 9)
        Convention -- Conflikt 8 (2015); Program book -- Pocket program
      - Conflikt 2015, January 30-February 1, Conflikt; 1 copy; Notes: This is a white covered booklet with a life presever on the cover and a swirl of musical notes. The guests were GOH: Cecilia Eng, Toastmaster, Alexander James Adams, Interfilk guest: Toyboat. Origin: Conflikt 2015 Convention: Conflikt 2015; genreform: Program booklet (Box 2)
      - Catechism of Filk, 2015; Parker, Carole; Laubenheimer, Bill; Ehrlich, Gary; Hayman, David; Hayman, Judith; Sloan, Kathleen; Eng, Cecelia; Nesbit, Andrew III; Patowski, Yvonne ""Catbunny""; 1 copy; Notes: Possibly the product of the Conflikt brunch where words are left on each table for the group to use to create a song. Origin: Conflikt 8, 2015 Convention: Conflikt 8, 2015; genreform: Song Lyrics (Box 9)
        Convention -- Conflikt 8 (2015); Song lyrics
    - Conflikt 9, 29 Jan 2016 to January 29-31, 2016
      - Conflikt Songbook, 2016; 1 copy; Notes: Pamphlet style, frogs on cover Origin: Convention: Conflikt 10; genreform: Songbook (Box 13)
        Convention -- Conflikt 10 (2017); Songbook
      - Schedule of events for Conflikt 2016, Conflikt 9 (2016); 2 copy; Notes: Printout Origin: Conflikt 2016 Convention: Conflikt 2016; genreform: Pocket Program (Box 9)
        Convention -- Conflikt 9 (2016); Program book -- Pocket program
      - Conflikt 2016 Program Book, Conflikt 9 (2016); 2 copy; Notes: Origin: Conflikt 9, January 29 - 31, 2016 Convention: Conflikt 2016; genreform: Program Book (Box 9)
        Convention -- Conflikt 9 (2016); Program Book
      - Cade Tinney - Conflikt 2016, Conflikt 9 (2016); 1 copy; Notes: Origin: Conflikt 2016 Convention: Conflikt 2016; genreform: Set List (Box 9)
        Convention -- Conflikt 9 (2016); Set list
      - Conflikt 9 Program book, Conflikt 9 (2016); 1 copy; Notes: Origin: Conflikt 9 Convention: Conflikt 9; genreform: Program booklet (Box 7)
        Convention -- Conflikt 9 (2016); Program booklet
      - Conflikt 9 Songbook, 2016; Conflikt 9 (2016); 2 copy; Notes: White with wizard and dragon Origin: Conflikt 9, January 29 - 31, 2016 Convention: Conflikt 9; genreform: Songbook (Box 9)
        Convention -- Conflikt 9 (2016); Songbook
    - Conflikt 10, 27 Jan 2017 to 29 Jan 2017
      - Conflikt 10 Schedule Grid, Conflikt 10 (2017); 2 copy; Notes: Two-color schedule grid Origin: Conflikt 10 Convention: Conflikt 10; genreform: Schedule Grid (Box 2)
        Convention -- Conflikt 10 (2017); Schedule Grid
      - Conflikt 10, 2017; Conflikt 10 (2017); 4 copy; Notes: White booklet Origin: Conflikt 10 Convention: Conflikt 10, January 27-29, 2017; genreform: Program booklet (Box 7)
        Convention -- Conflikt 10 (2017); Program booklet
      - Conflikt 10 Songbook, 2017; Conflikt 10 (2017); 1 copy; Notes: Origin: Conflikt 10 Convention: Conflikt 10, January 27-29, 2017; genreform: Songbook (Box 7)
      - Dr. Mary Crowell Setlist from Conflikt 2017, Conflikt 10 (2017); 1 copy; Notes: Songs include: Coffee Contata, Fairest of them All, Patchwork Cliche, Scattering Seeds on the Pomegranite Tour, Courting My Muse, Pandora's Box, Goliards, Jazz & Mai (the Ravenmay Waltz), Meet Me at the Labyrinth Plinth, October In July, Coffee With a Friend Origin: Convention: Conflikt 2017; genreform: Set list (Box 7)
        Convention -- Conflikt 10 (2017); Set list
    - Conflikt 11, 26 Jan 2018 to 28 Jan 2018
      - Conflikt 11 Pocket Program, 2018; Conflikt 11 (2018); 1 copy; Notes: White cover, pocket program, See/Speak/Hear No Evil frogs on cover Origin: Conflikt 11, January 26-28, 2018 Convention: Conflikt 11, January 26-28, 2018; genreform: Pocket Program (Box 9)
        Convention -- Conflikt 11 (2018); Program book -- Pocket program
      - Conflikt 11 Songbook, 2018; Conflikt 11 (2018); 2 copy; Notes: Cello close-up on cover Origin: Conflikt 11, January 26-28, 2018 Convention: Conflikt 11, January 26-28, 2018; genreform: Songbook (Box 9)
        Convention -- Conflikt 11 (2018); Songbook
    - Set list for a Cade Tinney Concert at a Conflikt, 1 copy; Notes: Participants include Betsey Tinney, Sunnie Larsen, Vixy, Tony, Mary Crowell, etc. Origin: Convention: Conflikt; genreform: Set list (Box 9)
      Convention -- Conflikt; Set list
    - Conflikt 2, 2009
      - Conflikt II Songbook, 2009; 4 copy; Notes: Music coming out of book with tardis, dragon and camera Origin: Convention: Conflikt 2: 2009; genreform: Songbook (Box 16)
        Convention -- Conflikt 2 (2009); Songbook
  - Confluence
    - Confluence 2005, 15 Jul 2005 to 17 Jul 2005
      Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania
      - CF-3, 2005; 1 copy; Notes: Mini - 006 sixth box of minidiscs #3 Origin: Convention: Confluence 2005; genreform: MiniDisc (Box 17)
        Convention -- Confluence 2005; MiniDisc
      - CF-4, 2005; 1 copy; Notes: Mini - 006 sixth box of minidiscs #4 Origin: Convention: Confluence 2005; genreform: MiniDisc (Box 17)
      - CF-5, 2005; 1 copy; Notes: Mini - 006 sixth box of minidiscs #5 Origin: Convention: Confluence 2005; genreform: MiniDisc (Box 17)
      - CF-6 Confluence 2005, 1 copy; Notes: Mini - 006 sixth box of minidiscs #6 Origin: Convention: Confluence 2005; genreform: MiniDisc (Box 17)
      - CF-7, 2005; 1 copy; Notes: Loose in box Origin: Convention: Confluence 2005; genreform: MiniDisc (Box 17)
      - CF2, 2005; 1 copy; Notes: Mini - 006 sixth box of minidiscs #2 Origin: Convention: Confluence 2005; genreform: MiniDisc (Box 17)
      - Confluence 2005 - 1, 1 copy; Notes: Mini - 006 sixth box of minidiscs #1 Origin: Convention: Confluence 2005; genreform: MiniDisc (Box 17)
    - Confluence 2006, 28 Jul 2006 to 30 Jul 2006
      - C6-6 Confluence 2006, 1 copy; Notes: Loose in box Origin: Convention: Confluence 2006; genreform: MiniDisc (Box 17)
        Convention -- Confluence 2006; MiniDisc
    - Confluence 2007, 27 Jul 2007 to 29 Jul 2007
      - C7-1, 2007; 1 copy; Notes: Mini - 004 fourth box of minidiscs #1 Outside of box says Confluence 2007 - six discs Origin: Convention: Confluence 2007; genreform: MiniDisc (Box 17)
        Convention -- Confluence 2007; MiniDisc
      - C7-2, 2007; 1 copy; Notes: Mini - 004 fourth box of minidiscs #2 Outside of box says Confluence 2007 - six discs Origin: Convention: Confluence 2007; genreform: MiniDisc (Box 17)
      - C7-3, 2007; 1 copy; Notes: Mini - 004 fourth box of minidiscs #3 Outside of box says Confluence 2007 - six discs Origin: Convention: Confluence 2007; genreform: MiniDisc (Box 17)
      - C7-4, 2007; 1 copy; Notes: Mini - 004 fourth box of minidiscs #4 Outside of box says Confluence 2007 - six discs Origin: Convention: Confluence 2007; genreform: MiniDisc (Box 17)
      - C7-5, 2007; 1 copy; Notes: Mini - 004 fourth box of minidiscs #5 Outside of box says Confluence 2007 - six discs Origin: Convention: Confluence 2007; genreform: MiniDisc (Box 17)
      - C7-6, 2007; 1 copy; Notes: Mini - 004 fourth box of minidiscs #6 Outside of box says Confluence 2007 - six discs Origin: Convention: Confluence 2007; genreform: MiniDisc (Box 17)
  - Conglomeration
    - Conglomeration, 2001, 10 Aug 2001 to 12 Aug 2001
      Louisville, KY
      - Thus Filked Zarathustra, 2001; Conglomeration, 2001; 1 copy; Notes: Spiral bound, off white cover with guitar playing sphinx Origin: Conglomeration, 2001 Convention: Conglomeration, 2001; genreform: Songbook (Box 10)
        Convention -- Conglomeration, 2001; Songbook
  - Consonance
    - Consonance 1991, 01 Mar 1991 to 03 Mar 1991
      - Consonance 1991 Program book, Consonance 1991; 1 copy; Notes: Pink pamphlet, Bob Laurent conchair Origin: March 1-3, 1991 Convention: Consonance 1991; genreform: Program booklet (Box 2)
        Convention -- Consonance 1991; Program booklet
      - Consonance flier, 1991, Consonance 1991; 1 copy; Notes: Pink pamphlet, list of upcoming events Origin: March 1-3, 1991 Convention: Consonance 1991; genreform: Flier (Box 2)
        Convention -- Consonance 1991; Flier
      - Consonance flier, 1991 with songs (progress report), Consonance 1991; 1 copy; Notes: Pink pamphlet Origin: March 1-3, 1991 Convention: Consonance 1991; genreform: Flier (Box 2)
    - Consonance 1992, 06 Mar 1992 to 08 Mar 1992
      - Consonance con-com newsletter #2, 1 August 1991; Consonance 1992; 1 copy; Notes: Pink pamphlet Convention: Consonance 1992; genreform: Flier (Box 2)
        Convention -- Consonance 1992; Flier
      - Consonance 1992 Program Book, Consonance 1992; 1 copy; Notes: With ads for Con-Chord Convention: Consonance 1992; genreform: Program booklet (Box 2)
        Convention -- Consonance 1992; Program booklet
      - Letter with finalized schedule for Consonance 1992, 27 February 1992; Consonance 1992; 1 copy; Notes: White with four sheets, including cover letter; genreform: Letter to Consonances program participants (Box 2)
        Convention -- Consonance 1992; Letter
    - Consonance 1993, 05 Mar 1993 to 07 Mar 1993
      - Consonance 1993, 1 copy; Origin: March 5-7 Convention: Consonance 1993; genreform: Flier (Box 2)
        Convention -- Consonance 1993; Flier
      - Consonance 1993 Program Book, Consonance 1993; 1 copy; Notes: White cover and purple pages, Guest of Honor Carol Roper, Toastmaster Gary Anderson Origin: March 5-7 Convention: Consonance 1993; genreform: Program booklet (Box 2)
        Convention -- Consonance 1993; Program booklet
    - Consonance 1994, 04 Mar 1994 to 06 Mar 1994
      - Consonance 1994, 1 copy; Notes: Purple cover, white pages, ad in the back for Consonance 1996. Was there no Consonance in 1995? Convention: Consonance 1994; genreform: Program booklet (Box 2)
        Convention -- Consonance 1994; Program booklet
    - Consonance 1996, 01 Mar 1996 to 03 Mar 1996
      - Consonance 1996, 1 copy; Notes: Pink cover, white pages, Bob Laurent is con chair Convention: Consonance 1996; genreform: Program booklet (Box 2)
        Convention -- Consonance 1996; Program booklet
    - Consonance 1998, 06 Mar 1998 to 08 Mar 1998
      - Consonance 1998, 1 copy; Notes: White booklet with Filkers at Play on the cover Origin: March 6-8, 1998 Convention: Consonance 1998; genreform: Program booklet (Box 2)
        Convention -- Consonance 1998; Program booklet
    - Consonance 1999, 05 Mar 1999 to 07 Mar 1999
      - Consonance 1999, 1 copy; Notes: White booklet with clams on the cover (Clam Chowder was the guest) Origin: March 5-7, 1999 Convention: Consonance 1999; genreform: Program booklet (Box 2)
        Convention -- Consonance 1999; Program booklet
    - Consonance 2000 (Y2K), 03 Mar 2000 to 05 Mar 2000
      - Consonance 2000 (Y2K), 1 copy; Notes: White booklet covered in bugs Origin: March 3-5, 2000 Convention: Consonance 2000 (Y2K); genreform: Program booklet (Box 2)
        Convention -- Consonance 2000 (Y2K); Program booklet
    - Consonance 2001: A Filk Odyssey, 02 Mar 2001 to 04 Mar 2001
      - Consonance 2001: A Filk Odyssey, 1 copy; Notes: White booklet, black cover Convention: Consonance 2001: A Filk Odyssey; genreform: Program booklet (Box 2)
        Convention -- Consonance 2001: A Filk Odyssey; Program booklet
    - Consonance 2002, 01 Mar 2002 to 03 Mar 2002
      - Consonance 2002: Consonantal Drift, Consonance 2002; 1 copy; Notes: Lavendar cover, white pages Origin: March 1-3, 2002 Convention: Consonance 2002; genreform: Program booklet (Box 2)
        Convention -- Consonance 2002; Program booklet
      - Consonance 2002: Consonantal Drift, Consonance 2002; 1 copy; Notes: Pink booklet, white pages Origin: March 1-3, 2002 in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/consonancebook.html Convention: Consonance 2002; genreform: Songbook (Box 2)
        Convention -- Consonance 2002; Songbook
      - Consonance 2002: Consonantal Drift: Grim's Law (Linguistics) G, D, B => K, T, P Capo's Second Law (Music) G, D, B => A, E, C#, 1 copy; Notes: Pinkish cover, staple bound in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/consonancebook.html Convention: Consonance 2002; genreform: Songbook (Box 14)
    - Consonance 2003, 07 Mar 2003 to 09 Mar 2003
      - Consonance 2003, 1 copy; Notes: Purple cover, white pages, Talis Kimberley GOH Origin: March 7-9 Convention: Consonance 2003; genreform: Program booklet (Box 2)
        Convention -- Consonance 2003; Program booklet
      - Consonance 2003: Silkfingers in Hith and Mystory, Consonantal Drift, Consonance 2003; 1 copy; Notes: Orange cover, white pages Origin: March 7-9 in-print (same version/edition): https://www.conchord.org/xeno/consonancebook.html Convention: Consonance 2003; genreform: Songbook (Box 2)
        Convention -- Consonance 2003; Songbook